let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "the ________function appends not more than n characters.",
    answer: "strncat()",
    options: [
      "strcat()",
      "strcon()",
      "strncat()",
      "none"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "if the two string are identical,then strcam()function returns",
    answer: "0",
    options: [
      "-1",
      "1",
      "0",
      "yes"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "which of the following accesses a variable in structure b?",
    answer: "b.var;",
    options: [
      "b->var;",
      "b.var;",
      "b-var;",
      "b>var;"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "which is an indirectional operator among the following?",
    answer: "*",
    options: [
      "*",
      "&",
      "#",
      "%"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "A function which calls itself is called a_________function",
    answer: "recursive",
    options: [
      "self",
      "auto",
      "recursive",
      "static"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Address stored in a pointer variable  is of type________.",
    answer: "integer",
    options: [
      "character",
      "Array",
      "integer",
      "Floating"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "stdout,stdin and stderr are?",
    answer: "File pointer",
    options: [
      "File pointer",
      "File descriptors",
      "streams",
      "Structures"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "How many values can a C Function return at a time.",
    answer: "only one value",
    options: [
      "only one value",
      "maximum two values",
      "maximum three values",
      "None"
    ]
  },
   {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Let X be an array.which of the following operations are illegal?",
    answer: "All of these",
    options: [
      "X++",
      "++X",
      "X*2",
      "All of these"
    ]
  },
   {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which header file should be included to use function like malloc() and calloc()?",
    answer: "stdlib.h",
    options: [
      "stdlib.h",
      "memory.h",
      "string.h",
      "dos.h"
    ]
  },
];
